Guide to the Yale Alumni Magazine Photographs
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Yale Alumni Magazine photographs
1917-1973
RU 694
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
8.5
The materials consist of photographs produced for or published in the. Included are photographs and artwork for specific articles, camera-ready cover art, and photographs of alumni gatherings and trips. Of particular note are the photographs for the Film Issue, 1968 May, and the May Day Issue, 1970 May.
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 48-A (YRG 48-A), Yale pictorial records and collections.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Scope and Contents
The materials consist of photographs produced for or published in the Yale Alumni Magazine. Included are photographs and artwork for specific articles, camera-ready cover art, and photographs of alumni gatherings and trips. Of particular note are the photographs for the Film Issue, 1968 May, and the May Day Issue, 1970 May.
Arrangement
The photographs are arranged in three series: I. Photographs used in the publication of the Yale Alumni Magazine, 1917-1973. II. Oversize. III. Folio.
Photographs; Yale Alumni Magazine; AYA (Organization); Yale University -- Pictorial works; Yale University -- Buildings; Yale University -- Sports; Yale University -- Students
- Photographs, 1917-1972; Series I
  - Alumni gatherings
    - Alumni Fund, Sesquicentennial celebration, 1940 January (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Commencement, 1938, 1958, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Connecticut testimonial dinner to the new U.S. Attorney (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - General, 1933 April 21 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Crossword puzzle contest ( Alumni Weekly ), 1925 January 16 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Golf, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Mory's, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Reception, 1958 May (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Sports events, Undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Yale Medal winners, 1957 March (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Yalies celebrating Elihu Yale's birthday on NBC radio (Rudy Vallee); Honorees for contributions to humanity; swearing in of Ambassador to Court of St. James, 1935-1947 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Unidentified events, 1913, 1937-1939 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Unidentified events, 1940-1942 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Unidentified events, Undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Articles
    - 1957 May--"Yale Key [Club]" (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - 1965 December--"Photography in America: 1850-1965" (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - 1966 March--Guthrie, Sir Tyrone (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - 1966 September--Film--"To Be a Man" (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - 1966 November--"Yale and the November elections" (Box 1, Folder 18-20)
    - 1966 December--"The freshman counselor" (Tim Tyler) (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - 1966 general, campus photos (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - 1966 general, contact sheets (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - 1966 general, illustrations (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - 1967 January--Buckley--Coffin--debate (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - 1967 March--Marc Chagall (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - 1967 March--"The new forms of ministry" (Divinity School) (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - 1967 March--"The foreign student at Yale" (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - 1967 April--"Perspectives on the world" (Dane Archer) (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - 1967 April--"Who is to serve" (Joseph Lieberman) (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - 1967 May--Campus Scenes (Peter Schlaifer) (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - 1967 June--"The Making of Prometheus" (Yale Rep production) (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - 1967 July--"Alumni seminars" (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - 1967 October--"Reporting the Cool--Medium War" (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - 1967 November--"Hallucinogenic drugs--a collision of values" (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - 1967 November--"Research into hallucinogens" (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - 1967 December--"Draft resisters" (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - 1967 December--"The long arm of the small town" (Box 2, Folder 38-39)
    - 1967 May--Scenes of New Haven (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - 1967 October--New Zion community (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - 1967 December--Vassar students (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - 1967 Yale University Theater (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - 1968 January--"Teaching in Harlem" (Mary Ellen Mark) (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - 1968 February--Child Care Center (Box 3, Folder 45)
    - 1968 February--"One little girl had never walked on snow before" (Box 3, Folder 46)
    - 1968 April--"The glass foundations of science" (Henk Vanderglow) (Box 3, Folder 47)
    - 1968 April--"Rough way up the mountain" (Charles Ives) (Box 3, Folder 48)
    - 1968 April--"An undergraduate view of teaching" (Box 3, Folder 49)
    - 1968 May--"Computer seminar at Yale" (Box 3, Folder 50)
    - 1968 May--"Pulsa: light as truth" (Film Issue) (Box 3, Folder 51)
    - 1968 May--"Art of the twentieth--century" (Film Issue) (Box 3, Folder 52)
    - 1968 May--"Film and the new media" (Film Issue) (Box 3, Folder 53)
    - 1968 May--"Five Yale film makers" (Film Issue) (Box 3, Folder 54)
    - 1968 May--"The magical media tour" (Film Issue) (Box 3, Folder 55)
    - 1968 May--New Haven redevelopment project (Box 3, Folder 56)
    - 1968 May--Rev. Martin Luther King, Jr. (Box 3, Folder 57)
    - 1968 June--"Assembling the alumni art show" (Maggie Scarf) (Box 3, Folder 58)
    - 1968 June--"God in a technological society" (Box 3, Folder 59)
    - 1968 June--"What is the meaning of all this" (6-day undergraduate festival) (Box 3, Folder 60-61)
    - 1968 July--"Yale employee strike" (Box 3, Folder 62)
    - 1968 July--Wilbur Cross Medal recipients (Box 3, Folder 63)
    - 1968 July--"Yale men over the years" (Box 3, Folder 64)
    - 1968 October--Cover art (Box 3, Folder 65)
    - 1968 October--"Free-form world of foam" (Box 3, Folder 66)
    - 1968 October--"The scouting game" (Box 3, Folder 67)
    - 1968 October--"Dimensions of medical consciousness" (Box 3, Folder 68)
    - 1968 October--"New Haven gets a college" (sketch by Lance Hiddy) (Box 3, Folder 69)
    - 1968 November--"As freshmen first we came to Yale" (Box 3, Folder 70)
    - 1968 November--"Living theater, I mean, you know…" (Blow-ups only) (Box 3, Folder 71-72)
    - 1968 November-- "Living theater, I mean, you know…" (Contact sheets) (Box 4, Folder 73-75)
    - 1968 November--"The University Amanuensis" ("The Battle of Bunker Hill" by John Trumbull) (Box 4, Folder 76)
    - 1968 November--Claes Oldenburg (Jonathan Price) (Box 4, Folder 77)
    - 1968 December--Cover art (Box 4, Folder 78)
    - 1968 December--"The kaleidoscope of coeducation week" (Box 4, Folder 79-80)
    - 1968 December--"The toy generation" (Sketches by Laurence Channing) (Box 4, Folder 81-83)
    - 1968 December--"Opening night at the United" (Box 4, Folder 84)
    - 1968--"Sciences at Yale" (Box 4, Folder 85)
    - 1968--"Yale Law Journal" (Box 4, Folder 86)
    - 1969 January--"The uncertain life of a visiting professor" (Raja N. Khuri) (Box 4, Folder 87)
    - 1969 January--"From the library roof" (Box 4, Folder 88)
    - 1969 February--"Riders on the earth together" (Contact sheets of poem by Archibald MacLeish) (Box 4, Folder 89)
    - 1969 February--"A machine for living in" (Box 4, Folder 90-92)
    - 1969 February--"Range practice" (Dean Acheson letters) (Box 4, Folder 93)
    - 1969 February--"Reflecting on Vietnam and the communications process" (Box 4, Folder 94)
    - 1969 February--"The coeducation squeeze" (Box 4, Folder 95)
    - 1969 February--Murray Gell--man, Barry Lorthian (Box 4, Folder 96)
    - 1969 March--"The Cole Porter years" (Box 4, Folder 97)
    - 1969 March--Yale Medal citations (Box 4, Folder 98)
    - 1969 March--"The whats, whys, and wherefores of R.O.T.C." (Box 4, Folder 99)
    - 1969 March--"A summer place" (Box 4, Folder 100)
    - 1969 April--"SDS" (design by Joel Katz) (Box 5, Folder 101)
    - 1969 April -- "Ferment in the Drama School" (photograph by Joel Katz) (Box 5, Folder 101A)
    - 1969 April--Cartoon from The New Yorker (Box 5, Folder 102)
    - 1969 May--"How Black Studies happened" (Glenn deChabert) (Box 5, Folder 103)
    - 1969 May--"The Worldgame game" (photos of Buckminster Fuller) (Box 5, Folder 104)
    - 1969 June--"University launches plans for new health care center" (Box 5, Folder 105)
    - 1969 June--"Yale in Chicago, briefly" (Box 5, Folder 106)
    - 1969 June--"The complications of turning words into deeds" (James Mann) (Box 5, Folder 107-108)
    - 1969 July--"An unsentimental leave-taking" (Box 5, Folder 109)
    - 1969 October--"Historians as Hercule Poirot" (Robin Winks) (Box 5, Folder 110)
    - 1969 November--"Letter from Berkeley" (Box 5, Folder 111)
    - 1969 November--"Dream games" (Box 5, Folder 112)
    - 1969 November--"Students, violence, and the changing university" (cover) (Box 5, Folder 113)
    - 1969 December--"Language and the brain" (Box 5, Folder 114)
    - 1969 December--"Rowing plans are announced" (news clipping) (Box 5, Folder 115)
    - 1969 December--"Saga of the unsung" (Box 5, Folder 116)
    - 1969 "Grad housing" (Box 5, Folder 117)
    - 1969 general (Box 5, Folder 118)
    - 1970 January--"Miracles, disenchantments, responsibilities" (Box 5, Folder 119)
    - 1970 February--"At the university" (Box 5, Folder 120)
    - 1970 February--"Trauma at Yale" (Box 5, Folder 121)
    - 1970 May--"New economics" (Stewart Udall) (Box 5, Folder 122)
    - 1970 May--"News makers" (May Day issue) (Box 5, Folder 123)
    - 1970 May--Demonstrators (May Day issue) (Box 6, Folder 124)
    - 1970 May--Graphics (May Day issue) (Box 6, Folder 125)
    - 1970 May--Scenes, campus (May Day issue) (Box 6, Folder 126)
    - 1970 May--Scenes, New Haven (May Day issue) (Box 6, Folder 127)
    - 1970 June (Box 6, Folder 128)
    - 1970 July (Box 6, Folder 129)
    - 1970 October--"Student politics journal" (not printed) (Box 6, Folder 130)
    - 1970 October, general (Box 6, Folder 131)
    - 1970 October, contacts and negatives (Box 6, Folder 132)
    - 1970 November, general (Box 6, Folder 133)
    - 1970 November--National Guardsmen; police (May Day) (Box 6, Folder 134)
    - 1970 December--African art (Box 6, Folder 135)
    - 1970 December--Conservatives (Box 6, Folder 136)
    - 1970 December--University news (Box 6, Folder 137)
    - 1971 January--University news (Box 7, Folder 138)
    - 1971 February--Clothes (Box 7, Folder 139)
    - 1971 February--Silver (Box 7, Folder 140)
    - 1971 February--University News (D. McClintok, drawings) (Box 7, Folder 141)
    - 1971 March, general (Box 7, Folder 142)
    - 1971 March--Willy Males (deserter) (Box 7, Folder 143)
    - 1971 March--Adam photo (Peabody) (Box 7, Folder 144)
    - 1971 April--Barber shops (Box 7, Folder 145)
    - 1971 April--Ocean photos (Box 7, Folder 146)
    - 1971 April--University news (Box 7, Folder 147)
    - 1971 May--Newton/Erikson (Box 7, Folder 148)
    - 1971 May--Tibetan art (Box 7, Folder 149)
    - 1971 May--University news (Box 7, Folder 150)
    - 1971 June--"Higher math in lower school" (Box 7, Folder 151)
    - 1971 June--Hospital (Box 7, Folder 152)
    - 1971 June--Saldie (Box 7, Folder 153)
    - 1971 June--University news (Box 7, Folder 154)
    - 1971 July--Steve West (Box 7, Folder 155)
    - 1971 July--University news (Box 7, Folder 156)
    - 1971 October--Taft Hotel (Box 7, Folder 157)
    - 1971 October--University news (Box 8, Folder 158)
    - 1971 November--Potto family (Box 8, Folder 159)
    - 1971 November--University news (class note profile) (Box 8, Folder 160)
    - 1971 December--Boredom (Box 8, Folder 161)
    - 1971 December--Funds for science (Box 8, Folder 162)
    - 1971 December--Quality market (Box 8, Folder 163)
    - 1971 December--University news (class notes) (Box 8, Folder 164)
    - 1971 Summer linguists (Box 8, Folder 165)
    - 1972 December (Box 8, Folder 166)
    - 1972 Scenes from Yale (Box 8, Folder 167)
    - 1973 January (Box 8, Folder 168)
    - "Highways" (not printed), undated (Box 8, Folder 169)
  - Athletics
    - Baseball, 1937-1955 (Box 9, Folder 170)
    - Basketball, 1940s-1955 (Box 9, Folder 171)
    - Crew, 1950s-1960s (Box 9, Folder 172)
      - Yale-Harvard regatta?, 1954-1955 (Box 9, Folder 173)
    - Fencing (Box 9, Folder 174)
    - Football and Crew dinner, 1957 March (Box 9, Folder 175)
    - Football (Box 9, Folder 175)
    - Co-ed touch, undated (Box 9, Folder 176)
    - Games, 1941-1960 (Box 9, Folder 177)
    - Practice, 1954-1960 (Box 9, Folder 178)
    - Spectators and sidelines, 1955-1960 (Box 9, Folder 179)
    - Golf, undated (Box 9, Folder 180)
    - Gym, 1955 (Box 9, Folder 181)
    - Ice hockey, undated (Box 9, Folder 182)
    - Lacrosse, 1954-1955 (Box 9, Folder 183)
    - Polo, circa 1963 (Box 9, Folder 184)
    - Sailing, undated (Box 9, Folder 185)
    - Soccer, 1954-1955 (Box 9, Folder 186)
    - Squash, undated (Box 9, Folder 187)
    - Swimming, 1950s-1960s (Box 9, Folder 188)
    - Track, 1937, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 189)
    - Wrestling, 1937-1960s (?) (Box 9, Folder 190)
  - Buildings (miscellaneous)
    - Archways and doorways (Box 9, Folder 191)
    - Construction (Box 9, Folder 192)
    - Exteriors (Box 9, Folder 193)
    - Interiors (Box 9, Folder 194)
  - General
    - Aardvark donated to Peabody Museum ( Alumni Weekly ), 1932 (Box 10, Folder 195)
    - American deputation to Paris inter--allied conference ( Alumni Weekly ), 1917 (Box 10, Folder 196)
    - Art Gallery, circa 1960s (Box 10, Folder 197)
    - Artists at work, circa 1960s (Box 10, Folder 198)
    - Battell Chapel service, undated (Box 10, Folder 199)
    - Boats and schooners, undated (Box 10, Folder 200)
    - Campus scenes, circa 1970 (Box 10, Folder 201)
    - Commencement, circa 1950s (Box 10, Folder 202)
    - Connecticut tercentennial ( Alumni Weekly ), 1935 (Box 10, Folder 203)
    - Contact prints (miscellaneous) (Box 10, Folder 204)
    - Drama, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 205)
    - [Yale] Hope Mission, circa 1950s (Box 10, Folder 206)
    - Iceberg near St. Anthony Harbor, undated (Box 10, Folder 207)
    - Maps and charts, undated (Box 10, Folder 208)
    - Medical electronics, circa 1950s (Box 10, Folder 209)
    - Musical events, circa 1960s (Box 10, Folder 210)
    - New Haven scenes, undated (Box 10, Folder 211)
    - Oberlin College, Bosworth Hall, undated (Box 10, Folder 212)
    - Outdoor scenes, undated (Box 10, Folder 213)
    - Outing Club, undated (Box 10, Folder 214)
    - "Pioneer" drawings, undated (Box 10, Folder 215)
    - R.O.T.C., circa 1960s (Box 10, Folder 216)
    - Reunion, circa 1950s (Box 10, Folder 217)
    - Singing groups, undated (Box 10, Folder 218)
    - Stained glass windows (Sterling Library) (Box 10, Folder 219)
    - WYBC radio station, circa 1950s (Box 10, Folder 220)
    - Woodstock (UPI photos) (Box 10, Folder 221)
    - Vietnam War (UPI photos) (Box 10, Folder 222)
    - Yale Band concerts (Box 10, Folder 223)
  - Student life and activities
    - Class room scenes (Box 11, Folder 224-225)
    - Conferences (Box 11, Folder 226)
    - Dormitory life, circa 1950s (Box 11, Folder 227)
    - Laboratory scenes (Box 11, Folder 228)
    - Leisure activities (Box 11, Folder 229)
    - Meal times (Box 11, Folder 230)
    - Moving day (Box 11, Folder 231)
    - Organized activities (Box 11, Folder 232)
    - Social activities (Box 11, Folder 233-235)
    - Studying (Box 11, Folder 236)
    - Street vendors (Box 11, Folder 237)
    - Touring (Africa?) (Box 11, Folder 238)
    - Volunteer work
      - with New Haven children (Box 11, Folder 239)
      - at Yale New Haven Hospital, undated (Box 11, Folder 240)
    - Walking through Old Campus (Box 11, Folder 241)
    - Miscellaneous photos (Box 11, Folder 242)
  - Trips (AYA)
    - Hawaii, undated (Box 12, Folder 243)
    - Japan, undated (Box 12, Folder 244)
    - Washington, D.C., undated (Box 12, Folder 245)
    - Unidentified (Box 12, Folder 246)
  - Unidentified photographs (Box 12, Folder 247-249)
- Oversize, Series II
  - Alumni Day (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Alumni Association Dinner, Circa 1912 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - 1916 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Articles
    - Unidentified Art, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Yale and November Political Elections, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Cover: Yale Club of St. Louis, February 1967 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Photographs by Joel Katz, May 1967 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Reading Room (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Photographs and Cover, May 1967 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Theatrical Cover, June 1967 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Commencement Procession, July 1967 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Notes from a Pot Smoker, 1967 November (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Cover, 1967 November (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Land of the Free, 1967 December (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Civil Rights Demonstrators, Alabama, 1967 December (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - The Long Arm of the Small Town, 1967 December (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Help They're Banging Down the Doors, January 1968 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Temple of the Body, January 1968 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Case for a Guaranteed Income, February 1968 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Busy life of a College Master, February 1968 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Robert Penn Warren: Voices in My Blood, March 1968 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - What Makes Scholander Swim, March 1968 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - The Art of Conversation, March 1968 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Charles Ives: The Rough Way Up the Mountain, April 1968 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Pulsa: Light as Truth, May 1968 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - What is the Meaning of All This?, June 1968 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Commencement, 1968 July (Box 14, Folder 17-18)
    - 1934 Reunion, 1968 July (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - What Ever Happened to the New Jerusalem? (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Thomas Bergin, 1968 October (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Change and Challenge in Medical Education, 1968 October (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - The Free--Form World of Foam, 1968 October (Box 14, Folder 21-22)
    - Druzhba I Mir, 1968 November (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - The Living Theatre, I Mean, You Know, 1968 November (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - Football, 1968 November (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - Zallinger the Dinosaur Man, 1968 December (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - Lars Onsager: Yale's First Faculty Nobelist--A Man of Rare Talent, 1968 December (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - Football Wrap--Up, 1968 December (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - Troubador on the Right, 1968 December (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - Claes Oldenburg, 1968 December (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - Opening Night at United, 1968 December (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - Ink Drawing, World War I Airplanes, 1968 December (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - Finding a Forest in the Trees, 1968 December (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - Harvard Photos, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 31)
    - The Chinese Food Syndrome, 1969 January (Box 14, Folder 32)
    - Methadone, 1969 February (Box 14, Folder 33)
    - A Machine for Living, 1969 February (Box 14, Folder 34)
    - The Loneliest Sport of All, 1969 February (Box 15, Folder 35)
    - The Coeducation Squeeze, 1969 February (Box 15, Folder 36)
    - Alumni Day, 1969 March (Box 15, Folder 36)
    - A Summer Place, 1969 March (Box 15, Folder 37-38)
    - Cover by Joel Katz, 1969 March (Box 15, Folder 39)
    - The Cage, 1969 April (Box 15, Folder 40)
    - Cover by Joel Katz, 1969 April (Box 15, Folder 41)
    - The Shape of Things to Come, 1969 April (Box 15, Folder 42)
    - The Family and Its Functions, 1969 April (Box 15, Folder 43)
    - The Preoccupation with the Last Six Weeks, 1969 May (Box 15, Folder 43)
    - World Game, 1969 May (Box 15, Folder 44)
    - Ruby's Fraternal Chaos, 1969 May (Box 15, Folder 45)
    - Yale in Chicago, 1969 June (Box 15, Folder 45)
    - An Unsentimental Leave-Taking, 1969 July (Box 15, Folder 47)
    - Commencement, 1969 July (Box 15, Folder 47)
    - Reflections on an Incarceration, 1969 November (Box 15, Folder 47)
    - From Big Holes Big Buildings Grow, 1969 December (Box 15, Folder 47)
    - An Interview with Mayor Lee, 1970 January (Box 15, Folder 48)
    - Stone Spirits, 1971 (Box 15)
    - Cover, 1970? May (Box 15, Folder 49)
    - The Amazing Invention of Horace Taft, undated (Box 15, Folder 50)
    - Ingalls Rink, undated (Box 15, Folder 51)
    - Lamp in Snow, undated (Box 15, Folder 51)
    - Wallace for President, circa 1968 (Box 15, Folder 51)
    - Art and Architecture Project, undated (Box 15, Folder 52)
    - Art and Architecture Building Roof, undated (Box 15, Folder 52)
    - Muppets: Sesame Street, undated (Box 15, Folder 53)
    - Gateway: unidentified, undated (Box 15, Folder 53)
    - Miscellaneous sketches, undated (Box 15, Folder 54)
- Folio, Series III
  - 1968 Articles
    - Payne Whitney Gym Cover, January (Box DR2F6)
    - St. Louis Arch, February (Box DR2F6)
    - Robert Penn Warren, March (Box DR2F6)
    - The art of conservation, May (Box DR2F6)
    - Pulse: light as truth, May (Box DR2F6)
    - Football (Box DR2F6)
    - The living theatre, I mean, you know, November (Box DR2F6)
    - Claes Oldenburg, December (Box DR2F6)
    - Confessions of the court, December (Box DR2F6)
  - 1969 Articles
    - Lasers: a technological revolution, January (Box DR2F7)
    - Lux et Musica, March (Box DR2F7)
    - The Cole Porter years, March (Box DR2F7)
    - A real University, April (Box DR2F7)
    - The cage, April (Box DR2F7)
    - Protean man, May (Box DR2F8)
    - Yale/New Haven, June (Box DR2F8)
    - Commencement, July (Box DR2F8)
    - Reunions, July (Box DR2F8)
  - Articles, 1971-1972
    - Sketches by Stevenson, 1971 (Box DR2F9)
    - The educated nurse, 1972 December (Box DR2F9)
    - Brewster at commencement, undated (Box DR2F9)